Elmo Roper Papers
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Correspondence, undated, 1909-1972
  - Subseries C: Professional, undated, 1940-1972
    - University of Bridgeport, 1966 (Box 26:1630)
    - V, 1966 (Box 26:1631)
    - Wa - Web, 1966 (Box 26:1632)
    - Wei - Wes, 1966 (Box 26:1633)
    - Will - Wils, 1966 (Box 26:1634)
    - Win - Wy, 1966 (Box 26:1635)
    - Y, 1966 (Box 26:1636)
    - Ab - Ad, 1967 (Box 26:1637)
    - Ag - Au, 1967 (Box 26:1638)
    - Art in America, 1967 (Box 26:1639)
    - Atlantic Council
      - February - August, 1967 (Box 26:1640)
      - September - November, 1967 (Box 26:1641)
    - Ba, 1967 (Box 26:1642)
    - Be - Bu, 1967 (Box 26:1643)
    - Blackwelder, Justin, 1967 (Box 26:1644)
    - Ca - Ch, 1967 (Box 26:1645)
    - Cl - Co, 1967 (Box 26:1646)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, May - October, 1967 (Box 26:1647)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, October - December, 1967 (Box 26:1648)
    - D, 1967 (Box 26:1649)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1967 (Box 26:1650)
    - Fa - Fo, 1967 (Box 26:1651)
    - Fr - Fu, 1967 (Box 26:1652)
    - G, 1967 (Box 26:1653)
    - Ha - He, 1967 (Box 26:1654)
    - Hi - Ho, 1967 (Box 26:1655)
    - Hu, 1967 (Box 26:1656)
    - I - J, 1967 (Box 26:1657)
    - K, 1967 (Box 26:1658)
    - Kurtz, Howard G., March, 1967 (Box 26:1659)
    - Kurtz, Howard G., May - July, 1967 (Box 26:1660)
    - Kurtz, Howard G., August - December, 1967 (Box 26:1661)
    - La - Li, 1967 (Box 26:1662)
    - Li - Ly, 1967 (Box 26:1663)
    - Ma, 1967 (Box 26:1664-1665)
    - Mc, 1967 (Box 26:1666)
    - Me, 1967 (Box 26:1667)
    - Mi - Mo, 1967 (Box 26:1668)
    - Mo - Mu, 1967 (Box 26:1669)
    - N, 1967 (Box 26:1670)
    - National Planning Association, 1967 (Box 27:1671)
    - O, 1967 (Box 27:1672)
    - P, 1967 (Box 27:1673)
    - Population Crisis Committee, January - April, 1967 (Box 27:1674)
    - Population Crisis Committee, May - July, 1967 (Box 27:1675)
    - Population Crisis Committee, August - December, 1967 (Box 27:1676)
    - Population Crisis Committee, Background, 1967 (Box 27:1677)
    - R, 1967 (Box 27:1678)
    - Redding, Connecticut, 1967 (Box 27:1679)
    - Roper [business], 1967 (Box 27:1680)
    - Roper [property in England], 1967 (Box 27:1681)
    - Roper Center, 1967 (Box 27:1682)
    - Sa - So, 1967 (Box 27:1684)
    - Sp - Sv, 1967 (Box 27:1685)
    - Saturday Review
      - January - March, 1967 (Box 27:1686)
      - April - May, 1967 (Box 27:1687)
      - June - July, 1967 (Box 27:1688)
      - August - October, 1967 (Box 27:1689)
      - November - December, 1967 (Box 27:1690)
    - T, 1967 (Box 27:1691)
    - U - V, 1967 (Box 27:1692)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1967 (Box OS)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1967 (Box 27:1693)
    - Wa - Will, 1967 (Box 27:1694)
    - Wils - Wy, 1967 (Box 27:1695)
    - Y, 1967 (Box 27:1696)
    - Ad - Ag, 1968 (Box 27:1697)
    - Ag - Am, 1968 (Box 27:1998)
    - Am, 1968 (Box 27:1699)
    - Am - At, 1968 (Box 27:1700)
    - Atlantic Union
      - January - June, 1968 (Box 27:1701)
      - July - October, 1968 (Box 27:1702)
      - November - December, 1968 (Box 27:1703)
    - Ba - Be, 1968 (Box 27:1704)
    - Bi - Bu, 1968 (Box 27:1705)
    - Ca - Ch, 1968 (Box 27:1706)
    - Ch - Cl, 1968 (Box 27:1707)
    - Co, 1968 (Box 27:1708)
    - Cr, 1968 (Box 27:1709)
    - Campaign to Check the Population Explosion, 1968 (Box OS)
    - Campaign to Check the Population Explosion, January - April, 1968 (Box 27:1710)
    - Campaign to Check the Population Explosion, April - November, 1968 (Box 27:1711)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1968 (Box 27:1712)
    - Da - De, 1968 (Box 27:1713)
    - Di - Du, 1968 (Box 27:1714)
    - E, 1968 (Box 27:1715)
    - F, 1968 (Box 27:1716)
    - G, 1968 (Box 27:1717)
    - Ha - He, 1968 (Box 27:1718)
    - He - Ho, 1968 (Box 27:1719)
    - Ho - Hu, 1968 (Box 27:1720)
    - I - K, 1968 (Box 27:1721)
    - Kurtz, Howard G. and Kurtz, Harriet B., 1968 (Box 27:1722)
    - La - Li, 1968 (Box 27:1723)
    - Li - Lu, 1968 (Box 27:1724)
    - Ma, 1968 (Box 27:1725)
    - Ma - Mc, 1968 (Box 27:1726)
    - Mc - Mo, 1968 (Box 27:1727)
    - Mo, 1968 (Box 27:1728)
    - Mo - Mu, 1968 (Box 27:1729)
    - Montgomery, Scott Company, 1968 (Box 27:1730)
    - Na, 1968 (Box 28:1731)
    - Na - Ni, 1968 (Box 28:1732)
    - O, 1968 (Box 28:1733)
    - P, 1968 (Box 28:1734)
    - Population Crisis Committee, January - July, 1968 (Box 28:1735)
    - Population Crisis Committee, July - December, 1968 (Box 28:1736)
    - Ra - Ri, 1968 (Box 28:1737)
    - Ri - Ru, 1968 (Box 28:1738)
    - Roper [business], 1968 (Box 28:1739)
    - Roper--Interviews with founding pollsters, 1968 (Box 28:1740-1742)
    - Roper Center and property in England, 1968 (Box 28:1743)
    - Sa - Se, 1968 (Box 28:1745)
    - Sh - Sp, 1968 (Box 28:1746)
    - Sp - St, 1968 (Box 28:1747)
    - St, 1968 (Box 28:1748)
    - Saturday Review, 1968 (Box 28:1749)
    - Ta - Um, 1968 (Box 28:1750)
    - Un, 1968 (Box 28:1751)
    - V, 1968 (Box 28:1752)
    - Wa - We, 1968 (Box 28:1753)
    - We - Wi, 1968 (Box 28:1754)
    - Wi - Wy, 1968 (Box 28:1755)
    - Y, 1968 (Box 28:1756)
    - Ab - Ag, 1969 (Box 28:1757)
    - Ag - Am, 1969 (Box 28:1758)
    - Am - An, 1969 (Box 28:1759)
    - An - Au, 1969 (Box 28:1760)
    - Advertising Council, 1969 (Box 28:1761)
    - Affiliate Artists, Inc., January - April, 1969 (Box 28:1762)
    - Affiliate Artists, Inc., May - July, 1969 (Box 28:1763)
    - Affiliate Artists, Inc., September - December, 1969 (Box 28:1764)
    - American Association for Public Opinion Research (AAPOR) Award, 1969 (Box 28:1765-1766)
    - American Association for Public Opinion Research, Gallup vs. Harris [1968], 1969 (Box 28:1767)
    - American University in Cairo, February - April, 1969 (Box 28:1768)
    - American University in Cairo, July - October, 1969 (Box 28:1769)
    - American University in Cairo, October - December, 1969 (Box 28:1770)
    - Atlantic Council
      - January, 1969 (Box 28:1771)
      - February - March, 1969 (Box 28:1772)
      - March - April, 1969 (Box 28:1773)
      - May, 1969 (Box 28:1774)
      - May - June, 1969 (Box 28:1775)
      - June, 1969 (Box 28:1776)
      - July - September, 1969 (Box 28:1777)
      - October - November, 1969 (Box 28:1778)
    - Audits and Surveys, 1969 (Box 28:1779)
    - Ba, 1969 (Box 28:1780)
    - Ba - Be, 1969 (Box 28:1781)
    - Be, 1969 (Box 28:1782-1783)
    - Bi - Bo, 1969 (Box 28:1784)
    - Bo - Br, 1969 (Box 28:1785)
    - Br - Bu, 1969 (Box 28:1786)
    - Bu, 1969 (Box 28:1787-1788)
    - Baldwin, W. Orville, 1969 (Box 28:1789)
    - Bentsen, William, 1969 (Box 28:1790)
    - Birthdays, 1969 (Box 28:1791)
    - Blackwelder, Justin, January - February, 1969 (Box 28:1792)
    - Blackwelder, Justin, March - July, 1969 (Box 28:1793)
    - Blackwelder, Justin, April - December, 1969 (Box 28:1794)
    - Can - Carter, 1969 (Box 28:1795)
    - Carter - Chas, 1969 (Box 28:1796)
    - Chr - Cl, 1969 (Box 29:1797)
    - Coc - Colm, 1969 (Box 29:1798)
    - Colv - Conh, 1969 (Box 29:1799)
    - Conn - Core, 1969 (Box 29:1800)
    - Corw - Cu, 1969 (Box 29:1801)
    - Campaign to Check the Population Explosion, January - March, 1969 (Box 29:1802)
    - Campaign to Check the Population Explosion, March - April, 1969 (Box 29:1803)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions
      - January, 1969 (Box 29:1804)
      - January - February, 1969 (Box 29:1805)
      - March - May, 1969 (Box 29:1806)
      - June - November, 1969 (Box 29:1807)
      - December, 1969 (Box 29:1808-1812)
      - Background, 1969 (Box 29:1813-1814)
    - Children's Television Workshop, 1969 (Box 29:1815)
    - Clients/Proposals, 1969 (Box 29:1816)
    - Clubs, 1969 (Box 29:1817)
    - Council on Social Science Data Archives, January - March, 1969 (Box 29:1818)
    - Council on Social Science Data Archives, April - October, 1969 (Box 29:1819)
    - Council on Social Science Data Archives, Background, 1969 (Box 29:1820)
    - Da - De, 1969 (Box 29:1821)
    - De - Di, 1969 (Box 29:1822)
    - Di - Do, 1969 (Box 29:1823)
    - Do - Dr, 1969 (Box 29:1824)
    - Dr - Du, 1969 (Box 29:1825)
    - Declaration of Atlantic Unity, January - June, 1969 (Box 29:1826)
    - Declaration of Atlantic Unity, July - September, 1969 (Box 29:1827)
    - Dinners and Luncheons
      - February, 1969 (Box 29:1828)
      - March, 1969 (Box 29:1829)
      - April - May, 1969 (Box 29:1830)
      - June, 1969 (Box 29:1831)
    - E, 1969 (Box 29:1832)
    - Elba Systems Corporation
      - January - February, 1969 (Box 29:1833)
      - March - July, 1969 (Box 29:1834)
      - August, 1969 (Box 29:1835)
      - September - November, 1969 (Box 29:1836)
      - December, 1969 (Box 29:1837-1838)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica
      - January, 1969 (Box 29:1839-1840)
      - February, 1969 (Box 29:1841)
      - March, 1969 (Box 29:1842)
      - April, 1969 (Box 29:1843-1844)
      - April - May, 1969 (Box 29:1845)
      - June, 1969 (Box 29:1846-1847)
      - July, 1969 (Box 29:1848)
      - August - September, 1969 (Box 29:1849)
      - October - November, 1969 (Box 29:1850)
      - December, 1969 (Box 29:1851)
    - Fa - Fe, 1969 (Box 29:1852)
    - Fe - Fi, 1969 (Box 29:1853)
    - Fi - Fo, 1969 (Box 29:1854)
    - Fo, 1969 (Box 29:1855)
    - Fr - Fu, 1969 (Box 29:1856)
    - Fu, 1969 (Box 29:1857)
    - Freedom & Union/ Federal Union, 1969 (Box 29:1858)
    - Ga, 1969 (Box 29:1859)
    - Ge - Go, 1969 (Box 30:1860)
    - Gr - Gu, 1969 (Box 30:1861)
    - Ha, 1969 (Box 30:1862-1863)
    - Heb - Hen, 1969 (Box 30:1864)
    - Her - Hey, 1969 (Box 30:1865)
    - Hi - Hoe, 1969 (Box 30:1866)
    - Hof - Hov, 1969 (Box 30:1867)
    - Hu - Hy, 1969 (Box 30:1868)
    - Hawkins, William E., Jr. [Bering Holdings, Ltd.], January - June, 1969 (Box 30:1869)
    - Hawkins, William E., Jr. [Bering Holdings, Ltd.], July - December, 1969 (Box 30:1870)
    - Haug Associates, Inc., January - July, 1969 (Box 30:1871)
    - Haug Associates, Inc., August - December, 1969 (Box 30:1872)
    - Henry Street Settlement House, January - February, 1969 (Box 30:1873)
    - Henry Street Settlement House, March - December, 1969 (Box 30:1874)
    - Home Life Insurance, January - May, 1969 (Box 30:1875)
    - Home Life Insurance, June - December, 1969 (Box 30:1876)
    - I, 1969 (Box 30:1877)
    - International Research Associates, Inc. (INRA), 1969 (Box 30:1878)
    - Invitations, 1969 (Box 30:1879-1881)
    - Jac - Jan, 1969 (Box 30:1882)
    - Jav - Ju, 1969 (Box 30:1883)
    - Job Coordination, 1969 (Box 30:1884)
    - Ka - Keo, 1969 (Box 30:1885)
    - Ker - Kr, 1969 (Box 30:1886)
    - Kurtz, Howard G. (War Control Planners), 1969 (Box 30:1887)
    - La - Le, 1969 (Box 30:1888)
    - Li - Lu, 1969 (Box 30:1889)
    - Maa - Mars, 1969 (Box 30:1890)
    - Mart - McC, 1969 (Box 30:1891)
    - McE - McG, 1969 (Box 30:1892)
    - McH - McK, 1969 (Box 30:1893)
    - Me - Mi, 1969 (Box 30:1894)
    - Mon - Moo, 1969 (Box 30:1895)
    - Mos - Mu, 1969 (Box 30:1896)
    - Martin, Bennett S., January - May, 1969 (Box 30:1897)
    - Martin, Bennett S., June - December, 1969 (Box 30:1898)
    - Moore, Hugh, 1969 (Box 30:1899)
    - Mailings/Memoranda, 1969 (Box 30:1900-1902)
    - Market Research Council, 1969 (Box 30:1903)
    - McGee Reception, October - November, 1969 (Box 30:1904)
    - McGee Reception, December, 1969 (Box 30:1905)
    - Montgomery, SCott & Company, January - March, 1969 (Box 30:1906)
    - Montgomery, SCott & Company, April - June, 1969 (Box 30:1907)
    - Montgomery, SCott & Company, July - December, 1969 (Box 30:1908)
    - Na - Ne, 1969 (Box 30:1909)
    - Ne - Ni, 1969 (Box 30:1910)
    - Ni - No, 1969 (Box 30:1911)
    - No - Nu, 1969 (Box 30:1912)
    - National Association of Railroad Passengers, 1969 (Box 30:1913)
    - National Book Committee, 1969 (Box 30:1914)
    - National Planning Association, January, 1969 (Box 30:1915)
    - National Planning Association, February, 1969 (Box 30:1916)
    - National Planning Association, March - November, 1969 (Box 30:1917)
    - O, 1969 (Box 30:1918)
    - Pa, 1969 (Box 30:1919)
    - Pa, 1969 (Box 30:1920)
    - Pe - Pi, 1969 (Box 30:1921)
    - Po - Pr, 1969 (Box 30:1922)
    - Population Crisis Committee, January - February, 1969 (Box 30:1923)
    - Population Crisis Committee, March - June, 1969 (Box 30:1924)
    - Population Crisis Committee, July - December, 1969 (Box 30:1925)
    - Ra, 1969 (Box 30:1926)
    - Re, 1969 (Box OS)
    - Re, 1969 (Box 30:1927)
    - Ri, 1969 (Box 30:1928)
    - Ri - Ro, 1969 (Box 30:1929)
    - Ro - Ru, 1969 (Box 30:1930)
    - Roper, 1969 (Box 31:1931)
    - Roper [business/farm], 1969 (Box 31:1932)
    - Roper Stock gifts, 1969 (Box 31:1935)
    - Roper Stock gifts--Replies, 1969 (Box 31:1936)
    - Roper Center
      - January, 1969 (Box 31:1937)
      - February, 1969 (Box 31:1938-1939)
      - March - May, 1969 (Box 31:1940)
      - June - August, 1969 (Box 31:1941)
      - November - December, 1969 (Box 31:1942)
      - Background, 1969 (Box 31:1943)
    - Regional Plan Association, January - April, 1969 (Box 31:1944)
    - Regional Plan Association, 1969 (Box 31:1945)
    - Railroads
      - A - F, 1969 (Box 31:1946)
      - G - Z, 1969 (Box 31:1947)
      - Photographs from Gyro Systems, 1969 (Box 31:1948)
    - Sa - Sc, 1969 (Box 31:1951)
    - Sc, 1969 (Box 31:1952)
    - Sc - Si, 1969 (Box 31:1953)
    - Sm - Sp, 1969 (Box 31:1954)
    - Sp - St, 1969 (Box 31:1955)
    - St, 1969 (Box 31:1956-1957)
    - St - Sy, 1969 (Box 31:1958)
    - Saturday Review, January - June, 1969 (Box 31:1959)
    - Saturday Review, July - December, 1969 (Box 31:1960)
    - T, 1969 (Box 31:1961)
    - Tiffany & Company, 1969 (Box 31:1962)
    - Traub Company, 1969 (Box 31:1963)
    - U, 1969 (Box 31:1964)
    - University of Bridgeport
      - January - February, 1969 (Box 31:1965)
      - March, 1969 (Box 31:1966)
      - April, 1969 (Box 31:1967)
      - May - December, 1969 (Box 31:1968)
      - Undated, 1969 (Box 31:1969)
    - V, 1969 (Box 31:1970)
    - Value Line
      - January, 1969 (Box 31:1971)
      - January - March, 1969 (Box 31:1972)
      - March, 1969 (Box 31:1973-1975)
      - April - May, 1969 (Box 31:1976)
      - June - July, 1969 (Box 31:1977)
      - July - October, 1969 (Box 31:1978)
      - November - December, 1969 (Box 31:1979)
      - December, 1969 (Box 31:1980-1982)
    - Wa - Wea, 1969 (Box 31:1983)
    - Web - Wet, 1969 (Box 31:1984)
    - Wh - Wir, 1969 (Box 31:1985)
    - Wo - Wy, 1969 (Box 31:1986)
    - Wertheim & Company, 1969 (Box 31:1987)
    - X - Z, 1969 (Box 31:1988)
    - Aa - Agn, 1970 (Box 32:1989)
    - Agr - An, 1970 (Box 32:1990)
    - Ar - Av, 1970 (Box 32:1991)
    - Audits and Surveys, 1970 (Box 32:1992)
    - American Association for Public Opinion Research (AAPOR), 1970 (Box 32:1993)
    - Atlantic Council, 1970 (Box 32:1994)
    - Atlantic Council, Background, 1970 (Box 32:1995)
    - Breisner, Harold, 1970 (Box 32:1996)
    - Ba - Bl, 1970 (Box 32:1997)
    - Bo - Bra, 1970 (Box 32:1998)
    - Bre - Burg, 1970 (Box 32:1999)
    - Burn - Bus, 1970 (Box 32:2000)
    - Bank of New York, 1970 (Box 32:2001)
    - Blackwelder, Justin, January - July, 1970 (Box 32:2002)
    - Blackwelder, Justin, August - December, 1970 (Box 32:2003)
    - C - Carl, 1970 (Box 32:2004)
    - Car - Cas, 1970 (Box 32:2005)
    - Ce - Cl, 1970 (Box 32:2006)
    - Coo - Cow, 1970 (Box 32:2007)
    - Coc - Con, 1970 (Box 32:2008)
    - Cr - Cu, 1970 (Box 32:2009)
    - Cards, 1970 (Box 32:2010)
    - Campaign to Check the Population Explosion, 1970 (Box 32:2011)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1970 (Box 32:2012)
    - Christmas, 1970 (Box 32:2013)
    - Da - De, 1970 (Box 32:2014)
    - Di - Do, 1970 (Box 32:2015)
    - Dr - Du, 1970 (Box 32:2016)
    - Declaration of Atlantic Unity, 1970 (Box 32:2017)
    - Dinners, 1970 (Box 32:2018)
    - Ec - Ei, 1970 (Box 32:2019)
    - El - Et, 1970 (Box 32:2020)
    - Elligett, Jane [Mrs. Raymond J.], 1970 (Box 32:2021)
    - Elba Systems
      - January - May, 1970 (Box 32:2022)
      - June - August, 1970 (Box 32:2023)
      - September - October, 1970 (Box 32:2024)
      - November, 1970 (Box 32:2025)
      - December, 1970 (Box 32:2026)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica
      - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 32:2027)
      - January - March, 1970 (Box 32:2028)
      - April - June, 1970 (Box 32:2029)
      - June, 1970 (Box 32:2030)
      - July, 1970 (Box 32:2031)
      - August - November, 1970 (Box 32:2032)
      - December, 1970 (Box 32:2033-2034)
      - Background, 1970 (Box 32:2035)
    - Fa - Fi, 1970 (Box 32:2036)
    - Fl - Fo, 1970 (Box 32:2037)
    - Fr - Fu, 1970 (Box 32:2038)
    - Freedom & Union/Federal Union [Streit, Clarence], 1970 (Box 32:2039)
    - Ga - Gol, 1970 (Box 32:2040)
    - Gos - Gu, 1970 (Box 32:2041)
    - Ham - Harr, 1970 (Box 32:2042)
    - Hart - Hay, 1970 (Box 32:2043)
    - Heb - Hen, 1970 (Box 32:2044)
    - Hew - Hof, 1970 (Box 32:2045)
    - Hol - Hot, 1970 (Box 32:2046)
    - Hov - Hu, 1970 (Box 32:2047)
    - Haug Associates, Inc., 1970 (Box 32:2048)
    - Hawkins, William, January - June, 1970 (Box 32:2049)
    - Hawkins, William, July - December, 1970 (Box 32:2050)
    - Home Life Insurance Company, 1970 (Box 32:2051)
    - I, 1970 (Box 32:2052)
    - International Research Associates, Inc., January, 1970 (Box 32:2053)
    - International Research Associates, Inc., February - December, 1970 (Box 32:2054)
    - J, 1970 (Box 33:2055)
    - Ka - Ki, 1970 (Box 33:2056)
    - Kn - Ku, 1970 (Box 33:2057)
    - La, 1970 (Box 33:2058)
    - Le, 1970 (Box 33:2059)
    - Li - Ly, 1970 (Box 33:2060)
    - Ma, 1970 (Box 33:2061)
    - Mc - Mi, 1970 (Box 33:2062)
    - Mon - Moo, 1970 (Box 33:2063)
    - Mor - Mu, 1970 (Box 33:2064)
    - Montgomery, Scott & Company, 1970 (Box 33:2065)
    - N, 1970 (Box 33:2066)
    - National Assocition of Railraod Passengers
      - January - February (Box 33:2067)
      - March - April (Box 33:2068)
      - April - August (Box 33:2069)
    - National Planning Association, January - March, 1970 (Box 33:2070)
    - National Planning Association, April - November, 1970 (Box 33:2071)
    - O, 1970 (Box 33:2072)
    - Pa - Pen, 1970 (Box 33:2073)
    - Per - Pu, 1970 (Box 33:2074)
    - Pratt, Wallace E., 1970 (Box 33:2075)
    - Population Crisis Committee, January - April, 1970 (Box 33:2076)
    - Population Crisis Committee, May - August, 1970 (Box 33:2077)
    - Q, 1970 (Box 33:2078)
    - Re - Ri, 1970 (Box 33:2079)
    - Ro - Ry, 1970 (Box 33:2080)
    - Roper Organizations, 1970 (Box 33:2083)
    - Roper Research Associates, 1970 (Box 33:2084)
    - Roper Center, January - May, 1970 (Box 33:2086)
    - Roper Center, June - December, 1970 (Box 33:2087)
    - Roper Center, Background, 1970 (Box 33:2088)
    - Schu - Si, 1970 (Box 33:2089)
    - Sa - Schm, 1970 (Box 33:2090)
    - Sm - Sp, 1970 (Box 33:2091)
    - Sta - Sti, 1970 (Box 33:2092)
    - Str - Sy, 1970 (Box 33:2093)
    - T, 1970 (Box 33:2094)
    - Tiffany & Company, January - June, 1970 (Box 33:2095)
    - Tiffany & Company, July - December, 1970 (Box 33:2096)
    - Traub Company, 1970 (Box 33:2097)
    - Ul - Up, 1970 (Box 33:2098)
    - Ur - Ut, 1970 (Box 33:2099)
    - University of Bridgeport, February - May, 1970 (Box 33:2100)
    - University of Bridgeport, June - December, 1970 (Box 33:2101)
    - V, 1970 (Box 33:2102)
    - V-70, 1970 (Box 33:2103)
    - Value Line
      - January - April, 1970 (Box 33:2104)
      - May, 1970 (Box 33:2105-2106)
      - June - July, 1970 (Box 33:2107)
      - September - December, 1970 (Box 33:2108)
    - Wa, 1970 (Box 33:2109)
    - Wea - Wee, 1970 (Box 33:2110)
    - Wei - Wey, 1970 (Box 33:2111)
    - Wh - Wi, 1970 (Box 33:2112)
    - Wo - Wy, 1970 (Box 33:2113)
    - Wisdom Hall of Fame, 1970 (Box 33:2114)
    - X - Z, 1970 (Box 33:2115)
    - A, 1971 (Box 33:2116)
    - Ba - Be, 1971 (Box 33:2117)
    - Be, 1971 (Box 33:2118)
    - Be - Bu, 1971 (Box 33:2119)
    - Ca, 1971 (Box 33:2120)
    - Ce - Cl, 1971 (Box 34:2121)
    - Co - Cu, 1971 (Box 34:2122)
    - Charities, 1971 (Box 34:2123)
    - D, 1971 (Box 34:2124)
    - E, 1971 (Box 34:2125)
    - Elba Systems, 1971 (Box 34:2126)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1971 (Box 34:2127)
    - F, 1971 (Box 34:2128)
    - G, 1971 (Box 34:2129)
    - Ha, 1971 (Box 34:2130)
    - He - Ho, 1971 (Box 34:2131)
    - Ho - J, 1971 (Box 34:2132)
    - K, 1971 (Box 34:2133)
    - L, 1971 (Box 34:2134)
    - Ma, 1971 (Box 34:2135)
    - Ma - Mu, 1971 (Box 34:2136)
    - N, 1971 (Box 34:2137)
    - O - Pi, 1971 (Box 34:2138)
    - Pl - Q, 1971 (Box 34:2139)
    - Ro - Ru, 1971 (Box 34:2140)
    - Ra - Ro, 1971 (Box 34:2141)
    - Sc - Se, 1971 (Box 34:2142)
    - Se - Si, 1971 (Box 34:2143)
    - Si - Sw, 1971 (Box 34:2144)
    - T - U, 1971 (Box 34:2145)
    - U, 1971 (Box 34:2146)
    - Va - War, 1971 (Box 34:2147)
    - Wat - We, 1971 (Box 34:2148)
    - Wh - Wy, 1971 (Box 34:2149)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 34:2150)
    - Contributions, 1972 (Box 34:2151)
- Series II: Articles, undated, 1937-1969
  - 1937-1944 (Box 34:2152)
  - 1945-1947 (Box 34:2153)
  - 1948-1950 (Box 34:2154)
  - 1951 (Box 34:2155)
  - 1952-1953 (Box 34:2156)
  - 1954-1956 (Box 34:2157)
  - 1957-1958 (Box 34:2158)
  - 1959 (Box 34:2159)
  - 1960 (Box 34:2160)
  - 1961-1963 (Box 34:2161)
  - 1964-1965 (Box 34:2162)
  - 1966-1969 (Box 34:2163)
  - Atlantic Union, undated (Box 34:2164)
  - undated (Box 34:2165)
- Series III: Speeches, Notes and Polls, undated, 1936-1969
  - Subseries A: Speeches, undated, 1937-1969
    - 1937-1939 (Box 34:2166)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 34:2167)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 34:2168)
    - 1944 (Box 34:2169)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 34:2170)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 34:2171)
    - 1948 (Box 34:2172)
    - 1949 (Box 34:2173)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 34:2174)
    - 1951 (Box 34:2175)
    - 1952 (Box 34:2176)
    - 1953-1955 (Box 34:2177)
    - 1955 (Box 34:2178)
    - 1957 (Box 34:2179)
    - 1958 (Box 34:2180-2181)
    - 1959 (Box 35:2182-2183)
    - 1960 (Box 35:2184)
    - 1961 (Box 35:2185)
    - 1962 (Box 35:2186)
    - 1963 (Box 35:2187-2188)
    - 1964 (Box 35:2189)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 35:2190)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 35:2191)
    - Arbor Day, University of Nebraska (Box 35:2192)
    - 1969 (Box 35:2193)
    - undated (Box 35:2194-2195)
  - Speech cards,1939-
    - Tea Speech, ca. 1939 (Box 35:2196)
    - Sales Executive Club, 1940 March 19 (Box 35:2197)
    - "Waht Customers Think of Utilities," Southeast Electrical Exchange Seventh Annual Conference, 1940 May 10 (Box 35:2198)
    - Tea Forum, 1940 May 31 (Box 35:2199)
    - "As Others See Us," Annual Convention of the American Gas Association, 1940 October 10 (Box 35:2200)
    - "What's Ahead--Internally," Associated Industries of Alabama, 1940 October 18 (Box 35:2201)
    - Investment Bankers Assocition, New York Rotary Club, and Bond Club of Boston, 1940-1941 (Box 35:2202)
    - Vocational Guidance Association, 1941 February 20 (Box 35:2203)
    - "The People Look at Gas Utilities," Fifteenth Annual Business Conference of the New England Gas Assocation, 1941 March 28 (Box 35:2204)
    - "Labor's Public Relations," Massachusetts Federation of Labor, 1941 June 14 (Box 35:2205)
    - Home Economics Convention, 1941 June 25 (Box 35:2206)
    - American Meat Institute Convention, 1941 October 6 (Box 35:2207)
    - "Public Opinion in this Crisis," Kewanee Woman's Club, 1941 November 6 (Box 35:2208-2209)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1941 December 1-5 (Box 35:2210)
    - "The people--During and After the War," New York Young Democrats Club, 1942 January 26 (Box 35:2211)
    - "The people--During and After the War," University of Minnesota Convocation, 1942 May 7 (Box 35:2212)
    - "War Time Morale," Spiegel Company, ca. 1942-1943 (Box 35:2213)